{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I went to the same high school as Madonna.",
            "options": [
                "Ruta",
                "Ryan",
                "Anastasia",
                "Amber",
                "Elisabeth"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I got my butt kicked by Jean Claude Van Damme.",
            "options": [
                "Pim",
                "Anastasia",
                "Ruta",
                "Robi",
                "Caity"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I once danced for 30 hours straight without caffeine (or drugs).",
            "options": [
                "Caity",
                "Mishka",
                "Liyanbing",
                "Anastasia",
                "Robi"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I have a fish named Bully, and he follows & swims alongside my finger.",
            "options": [
                "Amber",
                "Maryse",
                "Liyanbing",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Ryan"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I was on the show Blue's Clues as a little kid.",
            "options": [
                "Robi",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Caity",
                "Mishka",
                "Annika"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My ancestors are from five continents.",
            "options": [
                "Ruta",
                "Annika",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Anastasia",
                "Maryse"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I play the banjo.",
            "options": [
                "Ryan",
                "Mishka",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Pim",
                "Anastasia"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I can make my tongue look like it's split down the middle.",
            "options": [
                "Ruta",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Liyanbing",
                "Amber",
                "Maryse"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I used to snore so loud that I had to get surgery to fix it",
            "options": [
                "Ruta",
                "Robi",
                "Pim",
                "Amber",
                "Ryan"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "On my 18th birthday I was arrested for vandalizing a police car.",
            "options": [
                "Annika",
                "Maryse",
                "Caity",
                "Ryan",
                "Mishka"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have haunting dreams about penguins sometimes.",
            "options": [
                "Amber",
                "Maryse",
                "Robi",
                "Pim",
                "Liyanbing"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I nearly slept on the hotel floor of a now 3x Grammy winning artist back when I was a teen..",
            "options": [
                "Ryan",
                "Pim",
                "Caity",
                "Mishka",
                "Anastasia"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was in a horse stampede and barely survived. ",
            "options": [
                "Maryse",
                "Caity",
                "Amber",
                "Ruta",
                "Ryan"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have Synaesthesia, Hypergraphia, etc. ",
            "options": [
                "Liyanbing",
                "Anastasia",
                "Caity",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Amber"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know how to ride a bicycle.",
            "options": [
                "Mishka",
                "Anastasia",
                "Robi",
                "Ryan",
                "Maryse"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I auditioned for X-Factor USA and they told me I sing too quietly.",
            "options": [
                "Maryse",
                "Mishka",
                "Caity",
                "Elisabeth",
                "Amber"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I like to find stray kittens that have been abandoned by the cat mom, and raise it until I find them a new adoption family.",
            "options": [
                "Pim",
                "Liyanbing",
                "Ryan",
                "Anastasia",
                "Amber"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        }
    ]
}